#### **SUMMARY**

I am a highly skilled data scientist with over **4 years of experience** building **machine learning systems** for applications in **robotics**, **computer vision**, and **natural language processing**. My work has been **published** and **patented**, and I was invited to present it at both **MIT** and **Harvard**.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Senior Data Scientist** 

**Amazon Robotics** 

North Reading, MA, USA Jul 2020 – Present

• Developed ML systems for robotic item manipulation (e.g. grasp learning, damage prediction, damage detection)

- Developed optimization algorithms for mobile robot path planning
- Responsible for performance improvements worth +\$100MM/year
- Recipient of Inventor Award
- Paper published at internal conference (< 5% accepted)</li>

Data ScientistToronto, ON, CanadaHubdoc IncFeb 2017 - Jul 2018

- Developed LSTM-based NLP system for extracting accounting information from financial documents
- Deployed to production with 99% precision at 95% recall while reducing extraction time by 99.99%

### **EDUCATION**

**Harvard University** 

Cambridge, MA, USA

Master of Science in Data Science (GPA: 4.0)

Aug 2018 – May 2020

Scholarship in Applied Computation, Distinction in Teaching

University of California, Berkeley

Berkeley, CA, USA Aug 2012 – May 2016

Bachelor of Science in Industrial Engineering & Operations Research (GPA: 3.9)

• High Honors (magna cum laude), Frank Kraft Award, Phi Beta Kappa, Tau Beta Pi, Alpha Pi Mu

# **PROJECTS**

## **Physics-Informed Neural Networks**

<u>GitHub</u>

- Developed GAN framework for unsupervised learning of solutions to differential equations
- Workshop paper published at ICML 2022

ML Trading System Proprietary

- Developed LDA-based NLP system for trading US equities
- Deployed to production for real-time trading

# **Generative AI for Human Faces**

<u>GitHub</u>

- Developed ResNet VAE to generate human faces
- · Code published to GitHub

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Languages** : Python, Javascript/Typescript

Frameworks: PyTorch, React Native
Libraries: Numpy, Pandas, Scipy
Dev Tools: AWS, Git, Firebase, Docker